{
    "quizName": "name",
    "questions": [
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "answer",
            "question": "question for this",
            "correctAnswer": "correct",
            "wrongAnswer1": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer2": "answer"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "d",
            "question": "question 2",
            "correctAnswer": "a",
            "wrongAnswer1": "b",
            "wrongAnswer2": "c"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "d",
            "question": "question 3",
            "correctAnswer": "a",
            "wrongAnswer1": "b",
            "wrongAnswer2": "c"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "a",
            "question": "a",
            "correctAnswer": "b",
            "wrongAnswer1": "c",
            "wrongAnswer2": "d"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "",
            "question": "e",
            "correctAnswer": "",
            "wrongAnswer1": "",
            "wrongAnswer2": ""
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "",
            "question": "g",
            "correctAnswer": "",
            "wrongAnswer1": "",
            "wrongAnswer2": ""
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "",
            "question": "k",
            "correctAnswer": "",
            "wrongAnswer1": "",
            "wrongAnswer2": ""
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "",
            "question": "n",
            "correctAnswer": "",
            "wrongAnswer1": "",
            "wrongAnswer2": ""
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "answer",
            "question": "question ",
            "correctAnswer": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer1": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer2": "anwer"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "answer",
            "question": "question 2",
            "correctAnswer": "answer ",
            "wrongAnswer1": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer2": "answer "
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "spiderman",
            "question": "who is gamora?",
            "correctAnswer": "why is gamora?",
            "wrongAnswer1": "i don't know",
            "wrongAnswer2": "iron man"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "gorilla",
            "question": "this is another question?",
            "correctAnswer": "this is another question",
            "wrongAnswer1": "this is an answer",
            "wrongAnswer2": "potato "
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "Sledgehammer",
            "question": "what type of leaf is on the Canadian flag?",
            "correctAnswer": "Maple Leaf",
            "wrongAnswer1": "Dandelion",
            "wrongAnswer2": "Brick"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "Bob",
            "question": "What is Iron Man's name?",
            "correctAnswer": "Tony Stark",
            "wrongAnswer1": "Tony Stank",
            "wrongAnswer2": "Strony Tark"
        },
        {
            "wrongAnswer3": "answer",
            "question": "another question",
            "correctAnswer": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer1": "answer",
            "wrongAnswer2": "anwer"
        }
    ]
}